<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hike the Ministik!</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/trailheads/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hike the Ministik!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Hike The Ministik!</copyright>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/trailheads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fairbrother Corner Trailhead</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/trailheads/fairbrother-corner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/trailheads/fairbrother-corner/</guid>
      <description>Named for a former nearby land owner, Fairbrother corner provides you with immediate access to the Waskahegan Trail. When you walk past the gate the Waskahegan extends both directly east and directly south. There is ample parking here because there is no ditch to speak of and ample space between the road and the treeline. This means you can easily safely park multiple vehicles off the road.?</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="//localhost:1313/trailheads/fairbrother-corner/featured-fairbrotherCorner.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misasin Trailhead</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/trailheads/misasin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/trailheads/misasin/</guid>
      <description>Like the trail, this trailhead seems seldom used, but because it is situated along a quiet road, it offers plenty of parking space in any season. In season, you can pull off the road into the very shallow ditch or simply park as far off the road as possible if snow is factor.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="//localhost:1313/trailheads/misasin/featured-misasin.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waskahegan Berg Section - South Trailhead</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/trailheads/berg-south/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/trailheads/berg-south/</guid>
      <description>The Waskahegan Berg Section - South Trailhead is bit different from other Ministik trailheads in that there is no safe parking at the trailhead itself. But parking is very close nearby at the U of A Access Gate. Once parked near the gate, walk for about 3 minutes west, cross the road and ditch and access the trailhead to start your hike.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="//localhost:1313/trailheads/berg-south/featured-waskaheganBergSouth.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stove Lake Trailhead</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/trailheads/stove-lake-trailhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/trailheads/stove-lake-trailhead/</guid>
      <description>The Stove Lake Trailhead, named after a now completely dried up lake nearby, has best parking space among Ministik trailheads. Situated on a sharp curve the wide, sloped ditch between the road and the trailhead gate allows room for multiple vehicles. Even in winter there’s room along the road itself to park multiple vehicles safely.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="//localhost:1313/trailheads/stove-lake-trailhead/featured-stoveLake.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francis Edward Williams Trailhead</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/trailheads/few/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/trailheads/few/</guid>
      <description>This trailhead offers somewhat meager parking: one good-sized car can safely pull off the road and park in front of the gate here. If two people are driving Mini Coopers, then maybe two cars. 😃 When parking, beware of the steep ditches here. Especially in winter it&amp;rsquo;s all too easy to slide into the ditch where you&amp;rsquo;ll probably need AMA assistance to get you back out.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="//localhost:1313/trailheads/few/featured-few.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mandy Lake Road Trailhead</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/trailheads/mandy-lake-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/trailheads/mandy-lake-road/</guid>
      <description>The Mandy Lake Road trailhead is well-used in all seasons. Although it is at the end of Township Rd 502, past any local farmyards, it gets maintenance attention in all seasons. There is ample parking along the small pond side of the road. Please don&amp;rsquo;t block the gate even though it is seldom, if ever, used.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="//localhost:1313/trailheads/mandy-lake-road/featured-mandy-lake-road.jpg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U of A Field Station Access Road Gate</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/trailheads/uofa-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/trailheads/uofa-road/</guid>
      <description>It’s fair to say that the U of A Access Road Gate is the “front door” of the Ministik. The gated road leads to a former  U of A Research Station and although the facility seems to have been shuttered from many years, the road itself is periodically cleared of deadfall and other obstacles.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="//localhost:1313/trailheads/uofa-road/featured-ufaAccessRoadGate.jpg" />
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
